cdn-redfin.com 2018-06-30

# Redfin Privacy Policy

## This Privacy Policy is effective as of February 14, 2018. Your continued use of the Services constitutes your acceptance of these updated policies.

By visiting Redfin.com or making use of the Redfin Applications (together, the "Sites"), you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy and our [Terms of Use](https://www.redfin.com/about/terms-of-use). Some terms used in this Privacy Policy are defined in our Terms of Use. A term used only here is "cookie." A cookie is a small electronic file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows the site to recognize your computer. Cookies may store user preferences and other information. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some website features may not function properly without cookies.

### 1\. Information Collection, Use, and Opting Out

The types of information we collect depend on your level of engagement with the Sites. The higher the level, the more information we need to provide our Services.

A. All Redfin Website and Users of the Redfin Applications

From registered and unregistered users of the Sites, we automatically receive and record information whenever you interact with the Sites. This includes IP address data from our server logs, cookie information, the pages you request, and the URL of the site you came to the Sites from. From all users of the Redfin Applications ("App Users") we also collect the user resettable mobile device ID (such as the ID for Advertising on iOS and Android ID on Android) and your geo-location information so that we can interact with you to provide geo specific information, such as homes for sale near you and information about listing your home for sale. Your IP address serves the same function for website users. App Users can turn off our access to your geo-location by adjusting "location services" within your mobile device settings. We use the information listed above to help diagnose Site problems and performance, analyze trends, customize your experience on the Sites, provide targeted information about Redfin’s Services, and administer the Sites.

Cookies and opting out:

  * **Redfin Cookies** : We put Redfin cookies on your computer (including mobile device) to help us keep track of when you were last on the Sites, and what you last searched on the Sites. While you are free to disable cookies on your browser, we recommend that you leave cookies activated to use some of the most useful Redfin features. 
  * **Third-Party Cookies for Website Use Analysis** : We use third parties such as Google, comScore and Inspectlet to help us analyze how people are using the Sites, and those third parties are authorized to use cookies and other tracking technologies to access personal information of visitors to the Sites. Such access to and use of personal information by Inspectlet is governed by Inspectlet's privacy policy; to view Inspectlet's privacy policy, [click here](http://www.inspectlet.com/legal#privacy). We also use the Google Analytics Advertising service to provide us with demographic data about our users on an anonymous basis, and that Google service uses a cookie that can be recognized by Google or its affiliate DoubleClick when you visit other websites. 
  * **Opting Out of Google Analytics** : To prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, [click here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) for instructions. 
  * **Third-Party Cookies Used to Target Ads to You When You are on Other Websites** : We may share the information that you provide to us, and the information that we collect about you, with others (including advertising service providers and networks) to serve you ads tailored to your interests or to tailor ads that may be served to you on our Sites, as well as other websites and on social media networks. You may also see ads for Redfin on other websites and social media because we participate in advertising networks. Advertising networks allow Redfin to target our advertising to you through demographic, behavioral and contextual means. These advertising networks track your online activities over time by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of cookies, web-beacons and other methods. Advertising networks use this information to show you advertisements that they believe are tailored to your interests. The information our advertising network vendors collect includes information about your visit to our Sites as well as pages you have viewed, and the actions you have taken on the Sites. 
  * **Opting Out of Targeted Advertising** : If you do not wish to have us collect, use and share information about you to deliver targeted online advertising in this manner, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) and follow the instructions of how to opt-out. Please also note that most opt-out mechanisms are cookie-based and will only affect the specific computer (including mobile device) and browser that is used to submit an opt-out request. If you have multiple computers or change computers, or use multiple browsers, you will need to submit opt-out requests for each such computer or browser. In addition, if you delete, block or otherwise restrict cookies, you will need to renew your opt-out choices to ensure that any opt-out cookies remain effective. 
  * **Opting Out of Mobile Device ID Tracking** : Mobile device users may reset the identifier or opt-out of receiving interest based ads in their mobile apps. Android Users will need to open the “Google Settings” or “Settings” App -> Accounts -> Ads -> and Check the option “Opt out of interest-based ads.” You may also reset the Android advertising ID to a new randomly generated subpoena by tapping “Reset advertising ID.” Apple iOS users may turn off ad tracking using the Apple ID for Advertising by navigating through the following screens: Settings -> Privacy -> Advertising. On the Advertising screen, users may tap “Limit Ad Tracking” to opt out of receiving ads targeted to their interest, or they may reset their advertising ID. 
  * **Opting Out Generally** : The Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising program provides consumers with the ability to opt-out of having their online behavior recorded and used for advertising purposes. To opt-out of having your online behavior collected for advertising purposes (for example, serving Redfin ads to you on Facebook) [click here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) for instructions. Choices you make are both browser and device-specific. This means that, for example, if you opt out when using Safari on your phone, you will not be opted out on Firefox or on your laptop. 
  * **Do Not Track** : Some browsers have a ”do not track” feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. These features are not yet uniform, so we are not currently set up to respond to those signals.
  * **Flash Cookies** : We currently do not use flash cookies, but we may in the future. To control flash cookies, [click here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html). Why? Because flash cookies do not reside in your browser, so your browser settings will not affect them.

B. Registered Redfin Site Users (including Registered App Users)

We are required to obtain your name and email address as a condition of our licenses with the multiple real estate listing services (the MLSs) in order to allow you to access the full MLS listings. You give us this information when you create your Redfin account. When you give us this information at one of our events, or upon request, we will create a Redfin account for you and this Privacy Policy and our [Terms of Use](https://www.redfin.com/about/terms-of-use) apply. In addition, when you are signed in to your Redfin account and using Redfin through Facebook, Twitter, or any other third-party authorization service, we may make use of the data that they provide us to further customize your Redfin experience.

  * **My Redfin** : My Redfin is a feature that allows you to upload notes and photos about a property, save searches, add favorites and x-outs, and otherwise organize homes that may be of interest to you. We save all of this "My Redfin" information for your use later. It is stored with your Redfin account information. 
  * **Account Password Security** : Your Redfin account password is encrypted on our server, and is known only to you. 
  * **Account Updates** : By visiting your [My Redfin: Account Settings](https://www.redfin.com/myredfin/settings), you can correct, amend, add or delete personal information associated with your account. However, even after you update information, we may maintain a copy of the original information in our records.

C. Home Tours

When you submit a home tour request, we will ask for your tour date and time preferences, as well as your phone number. We will also ask some questions so that our agent can verify your identity. When you meet up with one of our agents at the home, the agent will ask you to verify your identity, and may even ask for a photo ID. At this point, your relationship with Redfin is not just online.

D. Redfin Clients

When you are getting ready to buy or sell a home and you start working with our coordinators and agents, you become a Redfin Client. As part of the home purchase or sale process, you will need to provide a lot of information as is customary for a home purchase or sale transaction. This information can include, without limitation, your name, address, phone number, email address, buyer loan pre-approval documentation and seller property information. We ask you, as a buyer, for loan pre-approvals from a mortgage broker or lender to determine which homes are in your price range, and to help you make an offer more quickly when you do find a home. You, as a seller, are legally required to disclose certain information about your property to prospective buyers. Once you sign a Listing Agreement or Buyer Agreement with us, your relationship with Redfin is governed by that agreement, as well as our online [Terms of Use](https://www.redfin.com/about/terms-of-use) and this Privacy Policy.

### 2\. Information Storage and Security

We store the information we collect from you in the United States. If you are located outside the United States and choose to use our Sites, we may store and process the information you provide to us in the United States.

We take administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect the information that we collect from or about you from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Please be aware, however, that no method of transmitting information over the Internet or storing information is completely secure.

### 3\. Information Sharing

We share your information with Redfin personnel in the normal course of business, and with Redfin’s corporate affiliates, including Redfin Mortgage, LLC, RDFN Ventures, Inc., Walk Score Management, LLC, and Title Forward. We also share some of your information with third parties.

A. **Registered Site Users (including Registered App Users)** : Occasionally, we share your information with other companies for purposes of marketing Redfin products or Services that may be of interest to you. In order to determine the types of information that may be of interest to you, we may combine the information that you give us and information about your usage of the Services with other personally identifiable information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) available from our records and other sources. Under our contracts with all of our marketing partners, they are not allowed to use your information for any purpose other than supporting and promoting our Sites. If you follow a link on our Sites to a third party site, its privacy policy governs the collection and use of information you provide on that site.

B. **Redfin Clients:**

  * **Public Record Information** : Please be aware that home sales and purchases are a matter of public record, and your name and address, the price you paid, your property taxes, and other information will be available from public sites regardless of the brokerage(s), if any, who assist in the transaction. We post on our Sites some information that typically becomes part of the public record of a home sale or purchase. 
  * **Non-Public Record Information** : We share information obtained from you that is not public record in order to facilitate your home purchase or sale transaction.
    * **Service Providers to all Redfin Clients** : Our agents work with third parties to process your home search and sale transaction, and must share your information with those third parties. Examples include MLSs and providers of software used for document preparation and electronic signing. 
    * **Partner Agents** : A Partner Agent is employed by or works with another brokerage and is not a representative or employee of Redfin. Partner Agents have contracted with us to provide Redfin-quality service to a wider range of customers. We'll refer you to a Partner Agent in our discretion. If you are referred to a Partner Agent for your home purchase or sale transaction, we share your information with that Partner Agent so they can assist you. Redfin is not responsible for the work performed or the services provided by Partner Agents in any manner. 
    * **Home Seller Service Providers** : As is customary as your home sales agent, we share your listing information with MLSs and other listing websites, such as Trulia.com and Zillow.com. We also share your listing information with listing vendors such as photographers, home staging experts and home repair professionals like plumbers and electricians, as needed. 
    * **Home Buyer Service Providers** : As is customary as your home purchase agent, we must share your buying information with inspectors, title companies, escrow agents, closing attorneys, lenders, and other third parties as needed to process your transaction. 
    * **Potential Buyers** : By law, we are required to disclose to potential buyers certain information you provide about your property. 
  * **Negotiations** : We also post on our Sites price offers and counteroffers. We do not post your name on our Sites without your permission but if the sale is closed, the price and the fact that you bought or sold your house at that price is a matter of public record.

### 4\. Information Deletion

You may delete your Redfin account by "Deactivating your Account" on your [My Redfin: Account Settings](https://www.redfin.com/myredfin/settings) page. We may keep a copy of your account information for our records.

### 5\. Email Communications

We communicate with account holders and Clients about their accounts and home tours, searches and sales by email. You may also subscribe to Listing Alert Emails with customized summaries of homes for sale. If you opt-in to also receive marketing email messages, Redfin may send you Redfin-related news, surveys or promotions. If you do not want to receive alerts or marketing email from us, please visit the Email Preferences section of your [My Redfin: Alerts & Emails](https://www.redfin.com/myredfin/alerts-settings) and/or click the unsubscribe link in the bottom of the unwanted email.

### 6\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

Redfin reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Services following the posting of changes to this policy will mean you accept those changes. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post the updated Privacy Policy here and may notify you by email or by means of a notice on our website.

### 7\. Children

The Sites are meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can email us. You can also write to us at the address listed at the end of this policy. Please mark your inquiries "COPPA Information Request."

### 8\. Contact Us

Please contact us if you have more questions. If you have any questions about this policy, please email us at [webmaster@redfin.com](mailto:webmaster@redfin.com). You can also write to us at: 1099 Stewart St, Suite 600, Seattle, WA 98101.
